<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ClassDocumentation>

	<ClassMembers name="Logger">
		<summary>
			Static class used for thread-safe logging.
			Writes timestamped log entries into per-day log files under the application Log directory.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="SafeExecutor">
		<summary>
			Static utility class responsible for safely executing synchronous and asynchronous actions
			with standardized error handling.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="IConnectionFactory">
		<summary>
			Interface for defining a factory class for a specific database connection creation.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="SqlServerConnectionFactory">
		<summary>
			Factory class for creating and initializing connections to the SQL Server database
			using configuration settings.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="IDBEntity">
		<summary>
			Interface defining the contract for database entities, ensuring they possess a unique identifier.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="Book">
		<summary>
			Represents a book entity in the library, containing details such as title, price,
			stock availability, and relationships to authors and genres.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="Author">
		<summary>
			Represents an author entity, storing the author's name and unique ID.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="Genre">
		<summary>
			Represents a genre entity, storing the genre category name and unique ID.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="Customer">
		<summary>
			Represents a customer entity, storing personal details and contact email.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="Loan">
		<summary>
			Represents a loan transaction entity, tracking the book, customer, loan status, dates, and price.
			Contains logic for updating status based on dates.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="DAOBase">
		<summary>
			Abstract base class for Data Access Objects.
			Provides a common structure and helper methods for database operations on entities.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="BookDAO">
		<summary>
			Data Access Object for handling database operations related to Books.
			Manages specific book-related operations and relation synchronization (Authors/Genres).
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="AuthorDAO">
		<summary>
			Data Access Object for handling database operations related to Authors.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="GenreDAO">
		<summary>
			Data Access Object for handling database operations related to Genres.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="CustomerDAO">
		<summary>
			Data Access Object for handling database operations related to Customers.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="LoanDAO">
		<summary>
			Data Access Object for handling database operations related to Loans.
			Manages complex loan logic including stock adjustments and tracking returned items.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="EntityControlBase">
		<summary>
			Abstract base class for UserControls that manage database entities.
			Handles common tasks like data loading, adding, updating, and deleting items safely.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="BookControl">
		<summary>
			UI Control for managing the collection of books.
			Allows viewing, adding, editing, and deleting books, as well as managing their authors and genres.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="AuthorControl">
		<summary>
			UI Control for managing the collection of authors.
			Allows listing, adding, and deleting authors.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="GenreControl">
		<summary>
			UI Control for managing the collection of genres.
			Allows listing, adding, and deleting genres.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="CustomerControl">
		<summary>
			UI Control for managing the collection of customers.
			Allows listing, adding, editing, and deleting customers.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="LoanControl">
		<summary>
			UI Control for managing loan transactions.
			Allows creating new loans, viewing ongoing and returned loans, and updating loan statuses.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="MainMenuControl">
		<summary>
			UI Control for the main menu navigation.
			Provides buttons to navigate to different entity management views.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ConnectionWindow">
		<summary>
			Startup window that handles the initial database connection process.
			Provides feedback on connection status and options to reload or close.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="MainWindow">
		<summary>
			The main application window that hosts the various entity management controls.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

</ClassDocumentation>